gemly.com 2019-02-15

# Privacy Policy | Gemly

**We have updated this Policy. It will go into effect on May 25th, 2018. You can access the previous Policy[here](https://gemly.com/Previous-Privacy-Policy).**

## **Privacy Policy  **

This Privacy Policy applies to all services requiring the provision of personal data, provided by Techland sp. z o.o. with its registered office in Ostrów Wielkopolski, Żółkiewskiego 3, 63-400 Ostrów Wielkopolski, Poland (the “Company”) through websites owned by the Company.

**Scope of application**

This Privacy Policy applies to the storage and processing of personal data of persons using Company websites (“Users”) available at the following addresses: techland.pl, playtesty.techland.pl, akademia.techland.pl, pomoc.techland.pl, purefarminggame.com, buy.tormentgame.com, dockets.dyinglightgame.com, dyinglightgame.com, techland.pl/gamejam, forum.techland.pl, dyinglightgame.com/speedrun-contest, dyinglightgame.com/badblood, dyinglightgame.com/registration, dyinglightgame.com/10in12, dyinglightgame.com/buy, dyinglightgame.com/gift, dyinglightgame.com/bounties, gemly.com (“Websites”). The rules of using the Websites can be found in the relevant regulations available at the following **link** (“Regulations”).

Personal data of Users are processed in accordance with the applicable regulations on personal data protection. The Company is a controller of personal data of Users as defined in Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (“GDPR”).

**Collection of personal data through the Websites**

The User's personal data is collected and processed depending on the manner in which the User uses the Websites. Personal data of the User may be collected and processed in connection with the provision of services offered by the Websites, including the setting-up of accounts by the User in the Websites, placing orders for products and services, making purchases, testing games, sending marketing offers, newsletters, using the forum for players, providing technical support for Users, answering questions and complaints, participating in competitions organised by the Company, filling in questionnaires concerning the Websites and making other functionalities of the Websites available. 

Providing personal data is voluntary, however, failure to provide data which are necessary to use a given service of the Websites may prevent the User from using this service, e.g. prevent the creation of an individual account with the Website, prevent access to the forum, prevent the provision of answers to inquiries and complaints, or prevent participation in competitions.

**Creating accounts in the Websites, ordering services, using forums**

In order to create an individual account in the Website, the User provides their data, i.e. e-mail address and password, by means of which they will log in to the Website. In order to access certain Websites, the User may also log in via Facebook - in case of using such option, the User's data will be retrieved by the Website and updated on an ongoing basis, however, the Company will not transfer the User's data to Facebook. While using the account, other data concerning the history of use, use of the account functionalities, etc. may also be processed. In this case, personal data of the User is processed in order to provide services offered by the Company in accordance with the Regulations, such as creating an individual account, ordering services and products, e.g. through a shop, downloading and searching for content, enabling testing of games, using a forum for players and communication tools. The processing of data for the above purposes is lawful, because it is necessary to perform the contract concluded with the User, i.e. to provide the above mentioned services (legal basis - Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR). 

**Complaints, questions and technical support**

In order to obtain information on the services provided or technical support for Users, the User may refer to the answers provided in the Websites under the FAQ tabs. The User may also send an inquiry directly to the technical support personnel by completing forms published in the Websites, or via e-mail. Moreover, the User may file a complaint concerning the Website using the contact data specified in the Regulations. 

When contacting for technical support, other questions or complaints, the User indicates their details, such as e-mail address, in order to be able to obtain answers to their questions or complaints. This data is processed for the purpose of providing information regarding questions and complaints. The data processing is lawful because it is necessary for the purposes resulting from the legitimate interests pursued by the Company (legal basis - Article 6(1)(f) of the GDPR). The legitimate interest of the Company consists in the necessity to respond to inquiries of Users and to process complaints.

**Competitions**

If the Company announces a competition on its website, the User may be asked to provide the personal data indicated in the relevant competition form in connection with entering such a competition. The data of the User participating in the competition are processed for the purposes of the carrying out of the competition, including the purpose of providing the results of the competition and prizes. The processing of data for the above purpose is lawful, because it is necessary for the Company to carry out the competition, i.e. to fulfil its obligations resulting from the organisation of the competition (legal basis - Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR).

**Newsletter**

Through the Websites, including in particular depending on the situation, when opening an individual account, ordering services and products, testing games, using forums, entering competitions, etc., the User may consent to direct marketing, i.e. receiving marketing information by electronic means, including via telephone or e-mail applications. In such a case, the basis for data processing will be the User's consent (legal basis - Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR). The marketing information provided in this manner may include, but is not limited to, information about the Company's services and products, questionnaires, newsletters, etc. The consent may cover a specific type of information, e.g. the consent may only relate to receiving newsletters. Consent may be given, for example, by selecting the appropriate option in the registration form or on pages within the Websites. This consent is entirely voluntary and is not a prerequisite for the use of the Websites. The User can opt out of receiving marketing information via electronic means at any time, e.g. through the settings of his individual account in the account panel or by clicking on the link included in the received e-mail containing marketing content.

**Analysis and research**

In the event of data collection for individual account creation, ordering services and products, using the forum, testing games, using technical support, submitting complaints and inquiries, participating in competitions, sending marketing information via electronic means, the Company may process user data for statistical and marketing analyses, developing marketing strategies and improving the quality of its services and products as well as the performance of the Websites. For this purpose, the Company may also use anonymous and non-anonymous questionnaires filled in by Users directly with the use of forms available on the Websites or sent by Users via e-mail or in any other way. The data processing for the above purposes is lawful because it is necessary for the purposes resulting from the legitimate interests pursued by the Company (legal basis - Article 6(1)(f) of the GDPR). The legitimate interest of the Company consists in processing the data of the Client and the User in order to improve the quality of services and marketing of the Company's services and products.

**Consent for personal data processing**

If the Company asks the User to consent to the processing of personal data, e.g. in connection with the electronic transmission of marketing information or in connection with the participation in new projects or initiatives of the Company, and the User has given such consent, the User has the right to withdraw his consent at any time, which will not affect the lawful processing of data until the consent is withdrawn.

**User rights**

Subject to applicable law, the User is entitled to demand access to and receive information about personal data processed by the Company, to update and rectify incorrect personal data, to exercise the right to limit the processing of personal data or to object to the processing of personal data, the right to delete data or, if applicable, the right to data portability. In some cases, the requirements of the law may limit the User's rights. In addition to the above rights, the User is always entitled to file a complaint with the supervisory authority, which is the President of the Office for the Protection of Personal Data.

**Data security and storage**

The Company declares that the data stored and processed by it are secured in a necessary manner in accordance with applicable legal regulations. The Company maintains appropriate technical and organisational security measures. Access to the User's personal data is granted only to employees who need the data in order to provide services and operate the Websites. 

Personal data of the User will be stored for as long as it is necessary to use an individual account, provide services, use a forum, test games, participate in a competition and provide technical support, prepare an answer to an inquiry or complaint, and no longer than for the period specified in the law or for the period of the statute of limitations of claims. Where the Company processes data for the direct marketing of its products and services, the data will cease to be processed for this purpose as soon as the User objects to the processing of their data. The User may also withdraw their consent to the sending of marketing information by electronic means at any time, and the information will no longer be sent after the withdrawal of consent.

**Data transfers**

The Company does not transfer the User's data to any third parties, unless such transfer is in accordance with the law, e.g. necessary to perform the service ordered by the User. Depending on the circumstances, your data may be transferred to other entities, in particular: companies of the Company's group, external service providers (including IT service providers, marketing agencies), accountants, lawyers, auditors/reviewers, courts or other entities entitled to receive such data under the law.  
Personal data are processed and stored exclusively in the countries of the European Economic Area.

**Redirecting to third party websites**

In the event that Users are redirected to websites of entities other than the Company (e.g. in order to purchase a selected product), the Company does not provide such entities with any personal data of the Users. To the extent that the functions or related websites visited by the User are not Company Websites, the Company is not responsible for the processing of personal data related to the use of these websites. In order to understand the principles of data processing on these websites, the User should refer to the privacy policies made available on these websites.

**Cookies**

Due to the continuous improvement of the comfort of using the Websites, some of their elements may use cookies. These are small text files sent to the User's computer to identify him, and to correct and speed up certain operations. Cookies are stored on the User's device, helping to identify the User and to adapt the website to the User's personal preferences. Most cookies contain the website address, storage time and a unique number. Other information collected automatically when the Users visit the Websites include IP address, domain name, browser type, operating system, etc. This data is collected by means of cookies, among other things. They are used to optimise the user experience and to collect anonymous, collective statistics that are used to better understand user preferences and improve the quality of the website.

Cookies used in the Websites collect anonymous statistical data, store information about participation in polls (without information about the outcome of a poll) and identify active sessions.  
By default, standard web browsers allow Users to store cookies on their device. If the User does not agree to the use of cookies, the settings of the browser should be changed. The User may also change these settings in such a way that the browser automatically accepts cookies or notifies the User about any attempt to save cookies on the device. More information about the settings for cookies can be found in the browser information. Disabling the storage of cookies on a browser does not prevent the User from accessing the Websites, but it may cause some inconvenience in using them.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

The Company may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by informing Users thereof by posting an updated version of the Privacy Policy on the Websites and informing Users thereof by sending an updated Privacy Policy to their e-mail addresses or by posting the relevant information directly on the User's account, in the case of Users with an account. For the above reasons, it is recommended that the User checks the current version of the Privacy Policy from time to time. If the User does not accept the changes in the Privacy Policy, he should stop using the Websites.

**Contact**

In case of any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or if the User wishes to exercise his rights regarding the processing of personal data, please use the contact information below:

**Contact details of the Company:**

Techland sp. z o.o.

ul. Żółkiewskiego 3 

63-400 Ostrów Wielkopolski

E-mail address: **[support@techland.pl](mailto:support@techland.pl)**
